Jai Hind, Namaskar to you Sir, first tell me about
Outlook and update it, a day
after Outlook, the fact is that the market is
not ready to bow down but it is very very
confident of it and you are seeing these full all sorts of trying to
generate right hi
son this to me what should it not be wrong but
bank February also Cancer Metals, let me
also tell you this dollar is Shivling Research and
Friends and of Powerful Territory
Development, whatever reminder will come, there is also Emerging
Market Scan, even then there is
trading profit and loss on questions, right now
I want to say that
whatever call we give to Anil Singh, if it is done
then it is for trading,
you are on both sides, keep it for two days,
gentlemen, because you will remember the stop loss, it is
for you, this is our and your faces,
now that is why it is said that if you do not do pollution here then there is a
stop loss, then
you will have to bear it, sir, what
we say throughout the day is absolutely important, that
these 20 have come, sir, if ₹500 goes out from here then
you people say  You will be left wondering if Edison did
not give a call, brother, no call, if it is fair to me, then that is why I am
telling you the question. It does
not mean that
I am bullish on the market, I am with you. I am
telling you this because here
I am wearing a tractor cap,
inverter or not, because the
rewards from here are not favorable for the investor. You are right
Anil ji, you are absolutely perfect and
absolutely right that
looking at the distorted pressure, for different investments from trading point of view also,
you
should be well appointed, then you were
not given any update. 266 67294 Godrej Consumer
780 Marg, please subscribe immediately by
keeping my stoploss of 1575 and the
closed
idea given to you, 1617, it went up four to five times, you
can book profit there, in front of that I had given a
realized buy, with a stoploss of 1888.
I still think that there is a
little over setting in this, Reliance Candy
Crush Smart back, market root Shami
Reliance & Strong and along with it I had distributed
Daddy Lakh Cadila.  497 is done brother the
target is 11010 now one day you can book
profit in software update bandhan bank you
two my brother friend start in a week
please tell me so the first solution will be sir
for you buy ICICI Lombard 1595 at 1672 there is
surplus of 1575 target of 1655
second buy biodata ke nickel 498c at 490
dream defect target of 515 there
is effect pension in sale send in daddy finance for
shop class ninth target of 102 and
second send Bank of Baroda 64064
stoploss of 66th child money target of 1461
ok
from the strike where you have to buy in
two click on it Islam but this is
your buying advice from 1595 to
1622 you have to buy 15
subscribers you have to buy around 40
subscribers and here
you will get one more subscribe
Shubhendu along with sale balance you go to
physical in Reddy  80 Pure